Privacy Policy – ~Pourri                                       

shop

* Shop
    
    ### Odor Fresheners

    ### The Funk Factory

    ### Bundle + Save

    ### Gifts

    ### Trending

    **Free Gift with Purchase of $45+**

    **Shop Limited Holiday Scents**
    
* Search  
    
* 
    
    **Sign in** to earn rewards
    
*   **0**

X* [
    
    ### Best Smellers
    
    Shop Funk fighting Faves](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/best-sellers)
* [
    
    ### Build A Bundle
    
    Save 20%](https://www.poopourri.com/pages/build-your-own-bundle)
* [
    
    ### Sale
    
    Save Up to 60%](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/sale)
* [
    
    ### The Funk Factory
    
    Tap! Play! Win!](https://www.poopourri.com/pages/tap-play-win)
* [
    
    ### Poo~Pourri
    
    Before-You-Go Toilet Fresheners](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/toilet-sprays)
* [
    
    ### Travel Collection
    
    Shop Travel-Sized Fresheners](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/gifts-for-travel)
* [
    
    ### Home~Pourri
    
    Multi-Purpose Odor Fresheners](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/home-pourri)
* [
    
    ### Pet~Pourri
    
    Pet Odor Fresheners](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/pet-pourri)
* [
    
    ### Pot~Pourri
    
    Smoke Odor Fresheners](https://www.poopourri.com/products/pot-pourri-high-hopes)
* [
    
    ### Sole~Pourri
    
    Shoe + Foot Odor Fresheners](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/sole-pourri)
* [
    
    ### Car~Pourri
    
    Car Odor Fresheners](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/car-pourri)
* [
    
    ### Baby~Pourri
    
    Diaper Pail Odor Freshener](https://www.poopourri.com/products/little-stinker-diaper-pail-odor-eliminator)
* [
    
    ### Pit~Pourri
    
    Full Body Deodorant](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/pit-pourri)
* [
    
    ### New!
    
    The Latest & Greatest](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/new)
* [
    
    ### Holiday Gifts
    
    Presents at Every Price](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/holiday-gifts-that-sleigh)
* [
    
    ### Buy With Prime](https://www.poopourri.com/pages/buy-with-prime)
* [
    
    ### Shop All Products](https://www.poopourri.com/collections/all-products)
* Search  

### Let's Talk

Search  

Odor Fresheners 

Gifts 

Trending 

### Let's Talk"

My Account
==========

  Forgot Password? [Manage Subscriptions Without Password](https://www.poopourri.com/apps/retextion)

Don't have an account? Create Account

Lost Password
=============

Lost your password? Please enter your username or email address. You will receive a link to create a new password via email.

Recover Password Go Back

Register
========

Loading...

**Sign in to earn rewards** Don’t have an account? Create an account

Sign In

Privacy Policy
==============

This is the web site of **Scentsible, LLC**.

Our postal address is  
**4901 Keller Springs**  
**Suite 106D**  
**Addison, TX 75001**

We can be reached via e-mail at **[questions@pourri.com](mailto:questions@pourri.com)**  
or you can reach us by telephone at **972.818.8200**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name and e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, name and address, telephone number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).

The information we collect is shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site .

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.

From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address.

From time to time, we make our _customer_ e-mail list available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address.

You may receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address.

Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by, sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.

Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them .

Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address, write to us at the above address.

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number.

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server that has an SSL certificate using at least 128-bit encryption. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

California Privacy Rights: For the purpose of California Civil Code §1898.83, we have disclosed our Privacy Policy above and provided users of the Site with a cost-free option to opt-out of our use of your Personal Information by third parties for marketing purposes.

Text marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send text messages about our store, new products, and other updates. Updates include Checkout Reminders. Webhooks will be used to trigger the Checkout Reminders messaging system.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.  

**THIRD PARTY** 

We allow third parties to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of others across the web and in mobile applications. These third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect information about your use of our website and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked, and conversion information. This information may be used by us and these third parties to analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising targeted to your interests on other websites and online services, and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used in this way, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).  
  
We may also work with third parties to serve ads to you on our behalf or on behalf of other advertisers on third-party platforms (such as Facebook or Google). As part of these ad campaigns, we or third-party platforms may convert information about you, such as your email address and phone number, into a unique value that can be matched with a user account on these platforms to allow us and others to serve you advertising that is customized to your interests. Note that the third-party platforms may offer you choices about whether you see these types of customized ads.  

**SMS/MMS MOBILE MESSAGING MARKETING PROGRAM**

We respect your privacy. We will only use information you provide through the Program to transmit your mobile messages and respond to you, if necessary. This includes, but is not limited to, sharing information with platform providers, phone companies, and other vendors who assist us in the delivery of mobile messages.  WE DO NOT SELL, RENT, LOAN, TRADE, LEASE, OR OTHERWISE TRANSFER FOR PROFIT ANY PHONE NUMBERS OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE PROGRAM TO ANY THIRD PARTY. Nonetheless, We reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, to avoid liability, or to protect Our rights or property. When you complete forms online or otherwise provide Us information in connection with the Program, you agree to provide accurate, complete, and true information. You agree not to use a false or misleading name or a name that you are not authorized to use. If, in Our sole discretion, We believe that any such information is untrue, inaccurate, or incomplete, or you have opted into the Program for an ulterior purpose, We may refuse you access to the Program and pursue any appropriate legal remedies.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Users of the Program that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of the information you provide through the Program to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please contact us at the following address:

Poo Pourri

4901 Keller Springs

Suite 106D  
Addison, TX 75001

This Privacy Policy is strictly limited to the Program and has no effect on any other privacy policy(ies) that may govern the relationship between you and Us in other contexts.

Freshen funky odors without funky ingredients—guaranteed

About

Quick Links

Legal

Contact

P: [972.818.8200](tel:972.818.8200 "tel:972.818.8200") F: 972.818.8201  
  
M-Th 8am - 5pm CST  
F       8am - 4:30pm CST  
  
INTERNATIONAL INQUIRIES[international@pourri.com](mailto:international@pourri.com "mailto:international@pourri.com")

### Let's Talk

### About

### Quick Links

### Legal

### Contact

P: [972.818.8200](tel:972.818.8200 "tel:972.818.8200") F: 972.818.8201  
  
M-Th 8am - 5pm CST  
F       8am - 4:30pm CST  
  
INTERNATIONAL INQUIRIES[international@pourri.com](mailto:international@pourri.com "mailto:international@pourri.com")
